{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084338559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084338559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084347354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084347354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 27e9ad8f-d813-4bb9-bce5-e7dec3a388cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-ba-za"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084372512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084372512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 27e9ad8f-d813-4bb9-bce5-e7dec3a388cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-ya-ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084380434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084380434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 27e9ad8f-d813-4bb9-bce5-e7dec3a388cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_yu-go-ba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084386441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084386441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 27e9ad8f-d813-4bb9-bce5-e7dec3a388cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-di-nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084391765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084391765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 27e9ad8f-d813-4bb9-bce5-e7dec3a388cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-di-nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084404394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084404393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 27e9ad8f-d813-4bb9-bce5-e7dec3a388cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-di-nyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084417936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084417936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GA"," userResponse":" GA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084420958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084420958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084422531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084422531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GE"," userResponse":" GE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084425966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084425966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084427540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084427540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GI"," userResponse":" GI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084430305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084430305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084431872","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084431871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" go"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GO"," userResponse":" GO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084434778","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084434777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" go"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084436334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084436334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GU"," userResponse":" GU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084439222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084439222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084441238","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084441238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084441413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084441412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084446938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084446938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084462475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084462475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084469353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084469352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 3c81ddb2-77a8-44d8-80cd-c668e688dc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084479398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084479398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084483560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084483560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084489700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084489700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084493966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084493966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084501044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084501043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084508494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084508494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084512971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084512971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084516963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084516963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084521137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084521136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084525170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084525170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084532471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084532471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084548755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084548754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 5480afef-cdbf-4e7f-af3d-c5519854b166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084575267","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084575267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 04815c72-8429-4a39-be3e-fc69659cf0b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mta_ha_mzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084581927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084581927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 04815c72-8429-4a39-be3e-fc69659cf0b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mlu_mka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084588623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084588623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_081205"," gameId":" 04815c72-8429-4a39-be3e-fc69659cf0b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ya_ha_chu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}